Inventory of the Slavic Book Dealer Catalogs
Department of Special Collections
- Chalidze Publications, 1983-1985/1986 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  Contains 4 catalogs (including doubles), some with stamps and/or handwritten notes. In Russian and English.
- The Chatham Bookseller (New Jersey), Oct 29, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  Contains a catalog, slightly damaged.
- Chekhov Publishing House of the East European Fund, Inc. (New York), March 1952-May 1953 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  Contains a leaflet / price list in Russian.
- Chekryzhov, Yury, and Valetchikov, Igor, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 17)
  Contains 2 typewritten catalogs with handwritten additions / marks, 53 pages total. In Russian (both in Cyrillic and in Latin transliteration) and English mostly, with some titles in other languages.
- Christie's East, 06.08.1994-12.19.1996 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  Contains a catalog and the Sotheby's leaflet "The Russian Sale".
- Clemens, Alfons, Slavica-Antiquariat [1 of 2], Dec 1983-1984; n.d. (Box 7, Folder 19)
  Contains typewritten catalogs and related correspondence, 94 pages total. In Russian and German mostly.
- Clemens, Alfons, Slavica-Antiquariat [2 of 2], 1983-1984; n.d. (Box 7, Folder 20)
  Contains typewritten catalogs, related correspondence, etc., with handwritten additions / notes / marks, 95 pages total. In Russian, English, and German mostly.
- Co-liber, Dom Handlowo-Wydawniczy (Poland), 05.20.1994 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  Contains a typewritten price list with a stamp and a handwritten note, 1 A3 page, with a photocopy of a clipping from "Gazeta o ksi??kach". In Polish.
- Collets [1 of 3], 1975-1985 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  Contains 3 catalogs in Russian (mostly in Latin transliteration) and in English. Incl. also 1 catalog in Czech and English.
- Collets [2 of 3], 1989/90-1991 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  Contains 7 catalogs with several enclosures.
- Collets [3 of 3], July 1980-11.29.993 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  Contains typewritten price lists, correspondence, e-mail printouts, etc., 15 items total.
- Columbia Records, 1930-1932 [?] (Box 8, Folder 1)
  Contains 2 catalogs in Ukrainian, Russian and English. Slightly damaged.
- Constantinoff, John M. [I.M.], 1929-05.06.1948; n.d. (Box 8, Folder 2)
  Contains catalogs / price lists (including one photocopy), 4 items total, some with numerous handwritten marks / notes, some are damaged.
- Valery [Valerii] Cool Books, 12.28.1987-02.03.1988 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  Contains typewritten correspondence, fragments / photocopies of price lists, etc., 5 pages total.
- Corvina Kultura (Budapest), 1983-1985 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  Contains 2 catalogs.
- Cragsmoor Books, May 3, 1982; n.d. (Box 8, Folder 5)
  Contains a price list / order form no.59, 4 pages total, and a catalog no. 47
- Croatian Book (Cleveland), n.d. (Box 8, Folder 6)
  Contains 2 identical catalogs, an addition to it (16 pages, typewritten), another catalog, a leaflet, a business card, and an order form / price list with handwritten notes / marks. In Serbo-Croatian and English.
- Culture Garden, Co., 1992/93 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Cyclamen Books (Antiquarian booksellers) [1 of 2], 02.15.1980-Nov 1992 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  Contains catalogs / price lists and correspondence. Typewritten, with handwritten notes; multilingual. 19 items total.
- Cyclamen Books (Antiquarian booksellers) [2 of 2], Dec 1993-July 1, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  Contains catalogs / price lists, typewritten, multilingual. 27 items total (including doubles).
- Cyrillica Bookstore, 05.01.1996 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  Contains an e-mail printout of a letter from Tygran Vardanian to Wojciech Zalewski, 2 pages.
- Czasopisma kulturalne w Polsce, 1996/1997 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  Contains a catalog with handwritten notes and several attached handwritten notes (on Post-it's). In Polish.
- Czech statistical bureau, 1995-1997; n.d. (Box 8, Folder 12)
  Contains 3 catalogs (with a few enclosed items) and a leaflet. In Czech and English.
- Czechoslovakian periodicals, 10.16 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  1991-05
- Czytelnik, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  Contains an editorial plan for 1991, in Polish.
- Q.M. Dabney and Co., Dec 7, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  Contains a typewritten catalog with marks / notes.
- Dailey, William and Victoria, Antiquarian Books, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 16)
  Contains a catalog / price list with numerous handwritten notes.
- Dalhousie University, Russian Micro-Project, 03.26.1984; n.d. (Box 8, Folder 17)
  Contains catalogs / price lists, some with handwritten notes, 4 items total. Multilingual.
- Datamics Inc., 03.02.1984-01.10.2000; n.d. (Box 8, Folder 18)
  Contains 4 catalogs / price lists, multilingual, slightly damaged.
- Davies Book Company Limited, July 10, 1975; n.d. (Box 8, Folder 19)
  Contains 2 business letters (one with a price list), one is typewritten and the other is a photocopy; 2 pages total.
- Dekker and Nordemann B.V. [1 of 2], 05.23.1978; 02.16.1979; n.d. (Box 8, Folder 20)
- Dekker and Nordemann B.V. [2 of 2], n.d. (Box 8, Folder 21)
  Contains a catalog and 2 enclosed price lists, multilingual.
- Desideráta Libri prohibiti, 05.14.1995 [?] (Box 9, Folder 1)
  Contains a typewritten catalog with handwritten notes, additions, and corrections.23 pages total, multilingual.
- Deuticke, Franz, Antiquariat, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Dialog [1 of 2], 1987-1992 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  Contains catalogs, newsletters, posters, etc., 11 items total. Multilingual.
- Dialog [2 of 2], 1993-1995; n.d. (Box 9, Folder 4)
  Contains catalogs / price lists, newsletters, posters, etc., 25 items total including doubles. Multilingual.
- Dom knigi 'Sankt-Peterburg' (Saint-Petersburg Publishing House and Entertainment Group), Oct-Dec 1997; May 4, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  Contains 4 catalogs (including doubles), one is slightly damaged. In Russian.
- Le Domaine Slave, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 6)
  Contains a catalog with several handwritten notes. In French.
- Domashnii spravochnik podpischika, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  Contains a catalog, damaged. In Russian.
- Dragulanesku, Nicolae (Romania), 1999 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  Contains a release, 1 page, with a handwritten note. In French.
- Druk (Ukraine), 2000 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  Contains 3 catalogs and 2 empty envelopes. (Some items are slightly damaged.) In Ukrainian.
- Dufour Editions Inc., July 10, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- East View Publications [1 of 9], 1985, 1987, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  Contains typewritten catalogs / price lists and releases, 18 items total. In Russian and English.
- East View Publications [2 of 9], 1993 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  Contains 2 catalogs; a release, 1 page; a photocopy of a catalog, 30 pages; and a typewritten letter with a handwritten note, 1 page. In Russian (both in Cyrillic and in Latin transliteration) and English mostly. Some items are slightly damaged.
- East View Publications [3 of 9], 1994 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  Contains 6 typewritten catalogs (including doubles), and a photocopy, 1 page. In Russian, Ukrainian (in Latin transliteration) and English mostly.
- East View Publications [4 of 9], 1995 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  Contains catalogs, newspapers, a business card, and correspondence, 12 items total. In Russian, Ukrainian (both in Cyrillic and in Latin transliteration) and English. Some items are damaged.
- East View Publications [5 of 9], 1996-1997 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  Contains an order form, a price list, a catalog, misc.
- East View Publications [6 of 9], 1998 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  Contains a catalog in a folder without a cover and a fax, 1 page. Multilingual.
- East View Publications [7 of 9], 1999 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  Contains a catalog in a folder without a cover and a newsletter.
- East View Publications [8 of 9], 2006 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  Contains a catalog (with a DVD enclosed), 2 price lists, and a newsletter. Multilingual.
- East View Publications [9 of 9], n.d. (Box 10, Folder 4)
  Contains newsletters, order forms, price lists, etc., 14 items total.
- Eastern Christian Publications, 01.01.1996 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- East-West Features [1 of 3], 1980-1981 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  Contains price lists, catalogs, and related correspondence, 15 items total (including doubles), in Russian (both in Cyrillic and Latin transliteration) and English.
- East-West Features [2 of 3], 1982-1987 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  Contains price lists, catalogs, and related correspondence, 17 items total. Multilingual.
- East-West Features [3 of 3], 1994; n.d. (Box 10, Folder 8)
  Contains price lists, catalogs, and misc. papers; 10 items total. In Russian (both in Cyrillic, pre-revolutionary spelling, and Latin transliteration) and English.
- Eddy, Albert, Book dealer (formerly AARDVARK Books), Canada, Feb 19, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  Contains a catalog with several handwritten notes on the front cover and marks inside.
- Edizioni Voland, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  Contains a catalog, in Italian.
- EDO s.p.o., Jugoslavija, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  Contains a price list, 3 pages, with postmarks and handwritten marks / notes. Slightly damaged. In Serbo-Croatian [?] mostly.
- Effect Publishing, Inc., d/b/a "Possev-USA", 1986-1987, 1995-1996; n.d. (Box 10, Folder 12)
  Contains catalogs, price lists, a questionnaire, etc., 11 items total. In Russian and English mostly. Some items are damaged, with handwritten notes.
- Emerald Isle Books (Northern Ireland), Spring 1973 (March 6, 1973) (Box 10, Folder 13)
- Encounter Books (Connecticut), May 3, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 14)
- The Enigma Press, Jan 1994 - Aug 1996 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  Contains 2 catalogs, multilingual.
- Erasmus, 1997-1998 (Box 10, Folder 16)
- Erudite [1 of 2], Dec 1992-1993; n.d. (Box 10, Folder 17)
  Contains catalogs, business cards, photocopies of correspondence, related documents; 11 items total (including doubles). Some items with handwritten notes. In Russian, English, and Ukrainian.
- Erudite [2 of 2], 1998-1999; n.d. (Box 11, Folder 1)
  Contains 6 catalogs (including doubles); a press release, 1 page; a typewritten letter with a handwritten signature, 1 page; and a typewritten price list, 9 pages. Some items with handwritten notes. In Russian, English, and Ukrainian.
- Europe Printing Establishment [1 of 2], 1970, 1973; n.d. (Box 11, Folder 2)
  Contains catalogs and price lists, some slightly damaged, with handwritten marks, 6 items total (including doubles). Multilingual.
- Europe Printing Establishment [2 of 2], 10.10.1974; 1980-1981; 08.02.1985; 1990; 1992; n.d. (Box 11, Folder 3)
  Contains a catalog, price lists, off prints, a photocopy of a clipping, correspondence; 8 items total. Multilingual.
- Europeriodiques S.A., Antiquarian Books and Periodicals, 12.17.1976 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  Contains a typewritten price list with numerous handwritten marks and notes. Multilingual.
- Eurora (European Research Association) / "Eurolingua", 1982 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  Contains a leaflet, in English and German mostly.
- Ex Libris [1 of 3], 1983-1985 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  Contains 6 catalogs, multilingual.
- Ex Libris [2 of 3], 1987; n.d. (Box 11, Folder 7)
  Contains catalogs, photocopies, brochures / leaflets, 22 items total.
- Ex Libris [3 of 3], n.d. (Box 11, Folder 8)
  Contains catalogs, one with a business card attached, 8 items total.
- Express Book Service, 06.28.1973; 02.18.1987; n.d. (Box 11, Folder 9)
  Contains catalogs / price lists, related correspondence, and a questionnaire, 11 items total. In Polish. Mostly typewritten, some with numerous handwritten notes.
- Les Éditeurs Réunis [1 of 4], 05.15.1938; n.d. (Box 11, Folder 10)
  Contains 3 releases and a price list; releases are damaged. In Russian (mostly pre-revolutionary spelling).
- Les Éditeurs Réunis [2 of 4], 1975-1982 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  Contains catalogs, 7 items total, some with handwritten notes.
- Les Éditeurs Réunis [3 of 4], 1984-1986 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  Contains 6 catalogs (including doubles), some with handwritten notes and / or damaged.
- Les Éditeurs Réunis [4 of 4], 1987-1993 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  Contains catalogs / price lists, 6 items total, one of them with "Effect Publishing Inc." stamps.
- Facets Video, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 1)
  Contains a newspaper catalog.
- Faculty Press (California), 1967 [?]; 1970s [?]; n.d. (Box 12, Folder 2)
  Contains "dust jackets", press releases, typewritten price lists / fragments, 11 items total (including doubles). Multilingual (in Russian mostly).
- Fallek, Claude, Guide des Librairies Spécialiseés de Paris, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  Contains a photocopy, 1 page. In French.
- Fam Book Service, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 4)
  Contains a catalog "Bulgarian periodicals", slightly damaged, multilingual, and a typewritten price list, in Russian and English mostly.
- Federal'naia sluzhba pochtovoi sviazi Rossiiskoi Federatsii (Federal Postal Service of Russian Federation), 1997 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Fertig, Howard, Inc., Publisher, 03.28.1973 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  Contains a release / price list, 1 page.
- Films - miscellaneous dealers [1 of 2], 03.26.1980-May 1991 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  Contains catalogs, releases, related correspondence; 9 items total, some with handwritten notes / marks and / or slightly damaged. In Russian and English mostly.
- Films - miscellaneous dealers [2 of 2], n.d. (Box 12, Folder 8)
  Contains catalogs, releases etc., 7 items total, some items with handwritten notes. Multilingual.
- Filozofické Fakulty Univerzity Karlovy, 1994-1997 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  Contains 2 catalogs from two different book dealers ("Interpress" and "Knihkupectví-Antikvariát"). In Czech, German and other languages.
- Finding-Aids on Microfiche (Moscow and Leningrad), 1976 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  Contains a catalog, heavily annotated. In Russian (mostly in Latin transliteration) and English. Slightly damaged.
- Wilhelm Fink Verlag, 1972 [?]-2006; n.d. (Box 12, Folder 11)
  Contains catalogs, one with an enclosure, and an e-mail printout; 5 items total (including doubles). Multilingual. One item is damaged.
- Firebird Publications Inc., 1992 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  Contains a catalog with a letter, 1 page, enclosed.
- Flegon, Alex, 01.17.2005; n.d. (Box 12, Folder 13)
  Contains a catalog with an appendix and an e-mail printout.
- Floorwood Ltd., 01.28-29.1981, Feb-April 1981 [?] (Box 12, Folder 14)
  Contains 5 typewritten price lists, one heavily annotated, with book request forms attached. In Russian (Latin transliteration) and English.
- Foreign Books Company, Winter 1985-Spring 1988 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  Contains catalogs / price lists, 15 items total, some with handwritten notes and / or slightly damaged. Multilingual.
- Forster, W., 03.23.1973 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  Contains a typewritten catalog / price list, multilingual, slightly damaged.
- Fort Ross Inc. (Russian-American Publishing Projects), 08.10.1998 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  Contains a release with photocopies of book covers / posters [?], 3 double-sided pages total. In Russian and English.
- Forum Ksi??ki, November 1999-11.08.2003 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  Contains 2 newsletters, in Polish.
- Four Continent Book Corporation [1 of 7], 1951-1952 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  Contains catalogs / price lists, 12 items total, some are slightly damaged. Multilingual.
- Four Continent Book Corporation [2 of 7], 1953; n.d. (Box 13, Folder 1)
  Contains catalogs / price lists and related materials, 14 items total, some with handwritten notes and / or slightly damaged. Multilingual.
- Four Continent Book Corporation [3 of 7], 1954 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  Contains catalogs / price lists and related materials, 12 items total, some with handwritten notes and / or slightly damaged. Multilingual.
- Four Continent Book Corporation [4 of 7], 1955; n.d. (Box 13, Folder 3)
  Contains catalogs / price lists and related materials, 16 items total, some with handwritten notes / marks and / or slightly damaged. Multilingual.
- Four Continent Book Corporation [5 of 7], 1956; n.d. (Box 13, Folder 4)
  Contains catalogs / price lists and related materials, 7 items total, some with handwritten notes and / or slightly damaged. Multilingual.
- Four Continent Book Corporation [6 of 7], 1957-1958; n.d. (Box 13, Folder 5)
  Contains catalogs / price lists and related materials, 14 items total, some with handwritten notes / marks and / or slightly damaged. Multilingual.
- Four Continent Book Corporation [7 of 7], 1961-02.07 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  1983.Contains catalogs / price lists, correspondence and related materials, 21 items total, some are slightly damaged. Multilingual.
- France Edition, 05.16[?] [n.y.] (Box 13, Folder 7)
  Contains an invitation, in French and Polish.
- Frank Cass Publishers, 1997-1998 (Box 13, Folder 8)
- Franklin, Burt, Bookseller and Publisher, 1946; n.d. (Box 13, Folder 9)
  Contains 2 catalogs, damaged. Multilingual.
- Front, Theodore, Antiquarian Books and Music, Nov 1979 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  Contains a photocopy of a price list with numerous handwritten notes / marks. Multilingual.
- Fundacja Nowa / "Nowa Foundation", 1991 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  Contains a catalog, in Polish.
- Fundusz pomocy niezale?nej literaturze i nauce polskiej, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 12)
  Contains a catalog / newsletter, in Polish.
- Futuristy, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 13)
  Contains a catalog / price list and a photocopy, 1 page; 2 items total, both with handwritten notes. Multilingual.
- Gelikon (Germany), 10.12.1986-09.26.1995 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  Contains 3 catalogs in Russian, a typewritten letter, 1 page, and 2 photocopies, 19 pages, with prices indicated. Some items are slightly damaged.
- General Microfilm Company, 10.15.1974 [?]-09.07.1990; n.d. (Box 13, Folder 15)
  Contains a catalog, related correspondence and other materials, 4 items total.
- A. Gerits [and Son(s)] (Amsterdam) [1 of 5], 1982 [?]-02.08.1984 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  Contains catalogs / price lists, related correspondence and other materials, 9 items total.
- A. Gerits [and Son(s)] (Amsterdam) [2 of 5], 1984 [?]-1986 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  Contains catalogs and related correspondence, 6 items total. Multilingual.
- A. Gerits [and Son(s)] (Amsterdam) [3 of 5], 1987-1988 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  Contains catalogs / price lists, related correspondence and other materials, 8 items total (including doubles), some with handwritten notes.
- A. Gerits [and Son(s)] (Amsterdam) [4 of 5], 1989-1990 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  Contains catalogs / price lists and related materials, 6 items total (including doubles), some with handwritten notes.
- A. Gerits [and Son(s)] (Amsterdam) [5 of 5], 1992-2000 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  Contains catalogs / price lists, 9 items total (including doubles), some with handwritten notes.
- Glagol, The Publishing House (Saint-Petersburg), 1995 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  Contains a leaflet, in Russian.
- Glas (Russia - UK), n.d. (Box 14, Folder 7)
  Contains a catalog / brochure.
- Gleboff, John A., "The Universal Agency", 1951-1961 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  Contains a catalog / leaflet, in Russian.
- Globe, International Antiquarian Books (Chicago), n.d. (Box 14, Folder 9)
  Contains a catalog / price list with an enclosed order form, slightly damaged. In Polish.
- Globus, A Slavic Bookstore [1 of 7], 1984/85-September 1989 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  Contains catalogs / price lists, 25 items total (may include doubles), some with handwritten notes, postal marks, enclosed receipts etc. In Russian mostly.
- Globus, A Slavic Bookstore [2 of 7], Jan 1990-1993 [?] (Box 14, Folder 11)
  Contains catalogs / price lists, 17 items total (including doubles), some with handwritten notes, postal marks etc. In Russian.
- Globus, A Slavic Bookstore [3 of 7], 1994-1997 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  Contains catalogs / price lists, 18 items total (including doubles), some with handwritten notes / marks. In Russian.
- Globus, A Slavic Bookstore [4 of 7], 1998 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  Contains catalogs / price lists, 24 items total (including doubles). In Russian and English.
- Globus, A Slavic Bookstore [5 of 7], 1999-2002; Jan-May 2006 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  Contains catalogs / price lists, 23 items total (including doubles). In Russian and English.
- Globus, A Slavic Bookstore [6 of 7], n.d. (Box 15, Folder 2)
  Contains catalogs / price lists, 41 item total (including doubles), some with occasional handwritten notes / marks. In Russian and English.
- Globus, A Slavic Bookstore [7 of 7], n.d. (Box 15, Folder 3)
  Contains catalogs / price lists, press releases, order forms, 30 items total (including doubles), and a photocopy of a draft [?], 1 page. With occasional handwritten notes / marks. In Russian and English.
- Globus Publishers, 10.14-23.1978; n.d. (Box 15, Folder 4)
  Contains typewritten and handwritten catalogs / price lists and related correspondence / other materials, 5 items total, some are annotated and / or damaged and / or incomplete. In Russian mostly.
- Goldberg, Yelena, 01.03.1999; n.d. (Box 15, Folder 5)
  Contains a catalog and a typewritten letter with a handwritten signature. In Russian and English respectively. Both items are slightly damaged.
- Michael Good, Fine and Rare Books, 04.03.1989 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  Contains a typewritten catalog / price list, posted.
- Anne M. Gordon Books, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 7)
  Contains a release [?], 1 page.
- Gosudarstvennaia ordena Lenina Biblioteka SSSR (USSR), 1986-11.01.1990 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  Contains 2 off prints from "Zapiski otdela rukopisei", slightly damaged. In Russian.
- Gosudarstvennaia publichnaia istoricheskaia biblioteka Rossii (Russia), 1993; 2000 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  Contains 4 microfiche catalogs, in Russian.
- Gosudarstvennaia publichnaia nauchno-tekhnicheskaia biblioteka Ordena Lenina Sibirskogo otdeleniia AN SSSR (State Public Science Library of the Siberian Branch of the Academy of Sciences, Novosibirsk, USSR), 1990 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  Contains a catalog with an enclosure, in Russian.
- Göttinger Antiquariat, 1985-1986 [?] (Box 15, Folder 11)
- Grant and Cutler Ltd., 06.14.2000; n.d. (Box 15, Folder 12)
  Contains 2 catalogs, one with a handwritten note on the front cover. Multilingual.
- Great Eastern Book Co., Sept 1971-11.16.1971 (Box 15, Folder 13)
- Grjebine, Les Editions (Paris), 05.23.1991-10.25.1992 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  Contains a catalog / price list, 2 pages; and invitation with an enclosed card; and a typewritten letter with a handwritten signature, 1 page. Multilingual.
- Grzybowski, Alicja (California), n.d. (Box 15, Folder 15)
  Contains 2 price lists, in Polish.
- A. Guering (Belgium), 12.09.1981 [?] (Box 15, Folder 16)
  Contains a typewritten catalog / price list, in Russian, with handwritten notes and with a posted envelope attached.
- Guilford Books (Virginia), 11.25.1974 (Box 15, Folder 17)
- Hall, Anthony C., Antiquarian Bookseller (England) [1 of 4], 02.27.1987; n.d. (Box 15, Folder 18)
  Contains a typewritten letter with a handwritten signature, 1 page, and catalogs / price lists no. 28, 36-37, 48-49
- Hall, Anthony C., Antiquarian Bookseller (England) [2 of 4], n.d. (Box 16, Folder 1)
  Contains catalogs / price lists no. 60, 68, 73-74, 78 (2 copies), 84 (2 copies). One catalog is heavily annotated. Multilingual.
- Hall, Anthony C., Antiquarian Bookseller (England) [3 of 4], n.d. (Box 16, Folder 2)
  Contains catalogs / price lists no. 85 (2 copies), 87-88, 101, 103 (2 copies), 104
- Hall, Anthony C., Antiquarian Bookseller (England) [4 of 4], n.d. (Box 16, Folder 3)
  Contains catalogs / price lists no. 107, 111-114, 117-118, 121, 125, 133, 134
- Hammer Mountain Book Halls (Schenectady, New York), n.d. (Box 16, Folder 4)
  Contains a catalog and a typewritten price list (slightly damaged). Multilingual.
- Hammersmith Books (London), n.d. (Box 16, Folder 5)
  Contains a catalog with numerous handwritten notes and marks. Multilingual.
- Harastej, George, 1993-1994 [?]; n.d. (Box 16, Folder 6)
  Contains 2 typewritten price lists, one heavily annotated, and related materials. In Russian mostly.
- Harrassowitz, Otto (Leipzig, Germany) [1 of 3], 1900-1906 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  Contains photocopies of catalogs, 4 items total, multilingual.